♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[in English] …is a master of disguise.
[in English] Do you know this man?
- [Audrey, in English] No.
- [cell phone clatters]
[Dmitri, in English]
I can help you find this man.
[in English] I know
a very good tracker, a man hunter.
[Samir, in English] Hello, Ambassador.
[in English] I think
we need the help of Mr. Dmitri.
Our target is Boss KM.
[Emerson] And the suitcase
with five million pesos.
What is this?
[Emerson] You'll wear that,
because that's the uniform
of Atoy's new breakout group.
I'm the OG child of Tatoy's thread.
[Audrey] Where is Ibyang?
Her real mother took her.
[Audrey] Who is she?
Why did she only show up now?
[in English] Good morning!
Come to my set. I need an extra actress.
Where is that?
Can I come with you?
No, you can't! Stay here!
[Charmi] You left her? Alone?
I won't miss my chance to be famous.
Feeling main character!
[goon actor 1] I'll riddle her
with bullets.
I'll use them all on her!
[Ibyang] Kill Mama?
- [in English] Action!
- [grunting]
[screaming and panicking]
PREVIOUSLY
Run now! Run!
[screaming and panicking]
Mama!
[objects clanging]
- [gasping]
- [squeals]
[objects clattering]
[in English] Cut!
[director] What's happening here?!
Get out of there!
[director] You're disturbing my set!
Who are you?!
You broke the equipment!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to!
"Sorry"?! Wait. Who are you?!
Hey, Al! Who is this?
- Whose child is this?!
- I don't know, Director.
- She just came in.
- What do you mean you don't know?!
You should know!
Hey. Who are you?
She's my mom.
[director] Huh?
- Olga?!
- [Olga] Director.
This is your child?
Why did you bring her to the filming?
Look what happened!
Director, I'm sorry.
She's just a child.
I'll take care of it!
Oh, so you'll take care of it!
The broken equipment
will be deducted from my budget!
[shrieks] You're driving me crazy!
And your dream, huh.
Your dream of fame?
Forget it.
Al, fix this!
[director] Back to one!
This is insane!
[somber music playing]
[director] Fix it, Al!
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
- [Karla] Brother Kurt.
- Oh?
Where's your costume?
- Oh, it's inside. Yes.
- Ah.
Here it is.
- Boss.
- Isn't Ame here yet?
- It's already nine o'clock!
- Looks like she's not coming.
We can't be late.
[phone ringing]
We should leave now. We might be late.
Hello? Where are you?
Look to your right.
[light music playing]
Are you leaving now?
Yes, we're just waiting for Sister Ame.
Remember what we talked about, okay?
Just follow our car. Okay?
[in English] Oh! okay. Copy, copy.
[Emerson] Psst, Karla.
Who are you talking to?
[Karla] No one, uh…
It's just T-Bak. She's pestering me.
You know.
[in English] T-Bak, okay.
Yes.
You're sure, huh.
- Oh, Ame's here.
- Hey!
[Karla] Oh, there she is.
She brought so much.
- [Emerson] Thank God you're finally here.
- Sorry!
- [in English] Thank you, Lord.
- [in English] Thank you.
I had to clean the shop, then Audrey came.
We chatted about Olga.
- Where's your uniform?
- Yes.
- Oh. I forgot.
- [Kurt] Yes.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Just get it later. Come on, it's late.
Oh! [chuckles]
Nice!
You're all wearing suspenders.
Are you going to dance?
- Oh, no, no.
- We could.
Well… Uh…
We're going on a field trip.
- Ah, field trip! Where?
- [Karla] Yes.
[stammering] To-- Uh, uh--
Ah, Miss Siony.
Don't you ever take a day off
from gossiping?
Even vehicles have number coding,
so they stop plying the streets.
You know, I'm just curious and concerned.
What if you don't come back
from that field trip?
Oh. That's exaggerated.
At least, someone knows
where to find you, and that's me.
That's too much.
"Won't be able to come back."
Miss Siony, thanks for the concern.
But we're not going to war.
- It's just a field trip.
- [Karla] Yes.
We're just going nearby.
We'll come back, promise.
- That's true.
- [Emerson] Okay then. Bye!
- Bye! We're leaving, Miss Siony!
- [overlapping chatter]
Okay, okay. We'll go ahead.
[Siony] Snacks. Don't you want some?!
- [Emerson] We're good. Bye!
- [Siony] Chips!
[Emerson] Bye, Miss Siony!
[Siony] Food for your trip.
[music fades]
[chuckles softly]
Hey.
Good thing you could come.
Brother Kurt couldn't come.
He had an emergency,
so we dropped him off
on the highway earlier.
I'm game for anything.
As long as I can help.
Wait. What's our group's name?
Child of the tailor?
Child of the tailor.
- Child of the thread!
- [Paldo] Oh?
That's minus points for the title.
Oh, make up for it!
[Paldo] Oh, sorry! My bad.
Wait. Does Atoy know I'm here?
I really want to make amends
for the mistakes I made against him.
I already convinced him.
I told him you're the replacement for now.
- So, you better make it up to me.
- [Paldo] Oh, there you go.
- You're something else, Emerson!
- Yes.
[Emerson] Okay, then.
No one gets off yet.
- I'll go first, just to observe.
- Okay, okay.
Wait for me.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
Oh.
Oh, Brother Emerso…
You're here too?
Yes.
What are you doing here?
Uh, uh…
Cathy and I have a date.
There's a famous restaurant there.
We'll eat there.
Date with Cathy.
[sneaky music playing]
Why are your nostrils flaring?
Looks like you're lying.
No!
Your father sent you here,
didn't he, to spy on us?
No! No!
It's not like that, promise.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
Don't mess with me, Gavin.
Don't mess with me.
[in English] Fine.
I followed you
because I found out you had a mission.
[in English] I just want to help you guys.
How did you know that?
Who told you? Karla?
Ah. No, no. No, sir, no.
I just overheard you talking.
[in English] Don't worry!
[in English] Your secret is safe with me.
[in English] I'm not here to sabotage you.
I also won't tell Dad, promise.
[in English] I just really
want to help you guys.
I promise, I promise.
I'm just here to help.
[suspicious music playing]
[music fades]
[Emerson] There, okay.
Let's check if it's all good.
- Thread 1, Thread 2.
- [Karla, in English] Copy.
Thread 3?
[in English] Loud and clear.
Thread 4?
[in English] Okay.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Target number 1.
Needle.
Kevin Martinez. He's the mastermind.
Target number 2. Scissors.
[Emerson] That's Boyet, the courier.
And the suitcase of money…
- [both] Buttons!
- [in English] Okay.
[phone rings]
[in English] Hello, Atoy?
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
Good morning, children of the thread.
[in English] Is everything in place?
- [both, in English] Yes, Master!
- [in English] Yes, Master.
Ah, Ame is with us.
And Paldo is here, replacing Brother Kurt.
We can handle this, Atoy.
[Atoy on the phone, in English] Very good.
I trust your abilities, but…
[in English] I just
have one last reminder.
[Atoy on the phone] No mission
is more important than your lives.
If you know it's dangerous,
abort immediately. Copy?
[all, in English] Yes, Master!
[in English] Good.
Make sure you don't get caught,
and most important of all, no one dies.
- [both, in English] Yes, Master!
- [in English] Yes, Master.
Atoy, thank you.
Thanks for letting me join.
Don't worry.
I won't fail them.
[in English] Good luck.
Uh, wait.
We have one more companion
that Atoy shouldn't know about.
Who?
- [in English] Hi, guys.
- Gavin?!
What are you doing here?
Brother caught me, so…
he allowed me to join.
What will your role be?
Mm-hmm.
He'll be the lookout
outside the function room.
He wasn't part of the original plan.
Oh, that's fine, whatever.
As long as I'm part of your adventure.
[in English] Okay. Ready?
[in English] Okay.
[in English] One, two, three…
- [all, in English] Let's go!
- [in English] Go!
What? What?
- What's that?
- I thought…
That's not Maalis, Taya!
What are you doing? Don't…
We're already wrong. We're just starting.
We'll stick together! Okay?
[in English] One, two, three…
- [all] You're it!
- Huh?
- Brother, what's that?
- Where did you get that?
What-- Let's just say "game".
Can we say "game" instead?
- [Karla] Okay!
- [in English] Game, okay?
One… Game, okay! Say "game", okay.
- [all] Game, game, game!
- [in English] Okay.
[in English] One, two, three.
[all, in English] Game!
[upbeat rock music playing]
Here are your badges,
clothes, and sandals.
[manager] Return them
after the event, okay?
[in English] Yes, ma'am.
[in English] Also, no heavy makeup.
Just glass skin.
Natural, but goddess-like look.
And once we start,
you'll welcome the guests.
[in English] Assist them to their seats.
And when the bid is awarded,
you'll approach the winning bidder
to have them sign the form.
Got it?
[all, in English] Yes, ma'am.
[in English] Also, you have to communicate
with them in English.
The bidders here are high-class.
[manager] You know that, right?
With all their money,
they don't even know where to spend it.
I wish I were like that.
[in English] Anyway, any questions?
[in English] We better get moving.
Come on.
[mid-tempo action music playing]
[music fades]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[whistling]
[in English] Oh, sorry.
I'll take this.
[giggles]
Okay. Right?
[in English] As always.
You're the best, Emerson!
So good, right?
[clears throat]
[whistling]
[suspicious music playing]
Thanks for doing my face.
I really don't know how to do makeup.
No worries, sis. You look beautiful.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Hi!
[in English] Mr. Alferez, please.
All right, um, kindly fill this out.
[in English] Sure.
- [in English] Number.
- [in English] Thank you.
- [in English] Mr. Alferez.
- [Alfarez, in English] Hi.
[in English] Let me
take you to your table.
[in English] Sure.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Thread 2, this is Thread 1.
I've arrived here too. Over.
[in English] This way, sir.
[in English] Thread 3, update on ETA.
[in English] This is Thread 3.
[in English] ETA unknown.
Huh? Why?
Mini Thread 4 had a wardrobe malfunction.
[Paldo on the device] But we're fixing it.
Hurry up. We need you here.
[in English] Okay, okay.
Uh, is it tight?
Here, attach the other side.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
- [in English] Hello.
- [in English] Yes.
[in English] Sorry.
The needle is here.
I repeat, the needle is here.
- [in English] Sir Kevin Martinez!
- [in English] Yes?
[in English] Let me
take you to your table.
[Kevin, in English] Thank you.
[in English] This way, sir.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[in English] This way, sir.
[in English] Sir, wine.
[in English] Thank you.
[upbeat rock music playing]
[usherette] Mr. Meneses.
That's me.
[music fades]
[in English] Hello, sir.
I'll take you to your seat.
[in English] This way.
[suspicious music playing]
[tense music playing]
[in English] Wine, sir, ma'am.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[intense music playing]
Good afternoon,
Ma'am Odette, Ma'am Malou.
[in English] Hello, Cathy!
[Cathy on the phone, in English]
Uh, babe, where are you?
Can we meet?
Ah, uh…
[Cathy on the phone, in English]
I'll be free in a few minutes.
I just accompanied Mommy to an event.
[suspicious music playing]
Sorry, I already have plans.
I went with Jason to Batangas.
[in English] I think
he's going to visit someone.
[in English] Oh, um…
Okay. Let's just talk tomorrow?
[in English] Yes, yes. Sure.
[in English] Okay, bye.
[muffled chattering]
[Cathy] All right.
[music swells]
[host, in English] Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
[in English] Welcome
to Palladium Auction House.
[in English] Tonight,
we have very exciting art pieces
for you to bid on.
[in English] Starting with…
With My Child's Hands.
[in English] Painted by Alexis Florence.
[in English] The starting bid
will be 100,000 pesos.
[in English] Do I hear 150?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] One-fifty, from number 17.
[in English] Two hundred!
[in English] Two hundred,
from the lady, number 22.
[in English] Three hundred.
Three hundred, again
from the gentleman, number 17.
[in English] Five hundred thousand!
[in English] Five hundred thousand pesos!
[in English] From the gentleman
of number 27.
[applauding]
Five hundred thousand for that?
Ibyang's drawing is even better.
Leave it alone. This is really
just a money-throwing event.
[Karla over device] I just hope
the money they're using
were obtained through clean means.
[in English] Do I hear 550?
[in English] Nothing?
[in English] Going once,
going twice.
[in English] Sold to the gentleman
of number 27.
[in English] Mr. Alferez, I believe.
[in English] Thank you so much.
[applauding]
[in English] Sir, please sign this.
- [melancholic music playing]
- [phone ringing]
[Atoy on the phone] Oh, Ibyang?
I'm on my way to work.
That's why I called you.
[Atoy on the phone] And yes, I miss you.
Ibyang?
Ibyang.
Are you there?
I broke something at Mama's work.
[sobbing]
She got scolded because of me.
[ibyang sobbing]
Maybe Mama doesn't want me
to be her child anymore.
[sobbing]
[scoffs]
What are you saying, Ibyang?
Don't say that.
If you made a mistake, then apologize.
But most important of all, make up for it.
How?
[Atoy on the phone] Simple.
Be good.
Then tell her,
"I won't do it again."
Right?
Ibyang, your mother
searched for you for so long.
Right? I'm sure she loves you very much.
She'll understand you.
But she's not talking to me.
[sobs]
Maybe she'll leave me again.
Ibyang, Ibyang,
no parent would do that to their child
just because of one mistake.
I'm sure she loves you.
I just wish
you were here with me.
But we're here.
We're just here, okay.
You're with us, and I'll never leave you.
Remember that.
[melodramatic music playing]
[Audrey on the phone, in English]
Dad, I'll be a little late.
[in English] It's traffic.
[in English] Don't worry, dear.
The people I'm meeting with
aren't here yet.
[in English] I'll see you in a while.
[in English] Bye-bye.
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[somber music playing]
[Dmitri, in English] Gentlemen!
[in English] Have your seat.
[in English] Thank you.
[in English] To what
do I owe this pleasure?
[in Russian/English] Good day, Mr. Dmitri!
[in English] We spoke
with Ambassador Petrov.
[in English] And he said
maybe you can help us.
[in English] Do you have a tracker?
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Yes.
[in English] Is he good?
[in English] Yes, very.
[in English] Is there something or someone
you need to find?
[security officer, in English]
This man, Mr. Regalia.
[in English] He broke into our embassy
and stole from us.
[clears throat]
[in English] Is there
something wrong, Mr. Regalia?
[rousing music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
[Audrey, in English] I think
you've got the wrong idea.
[in English] What is the matter?
You have another lover?
[in English] Maybe he's good in bed.
[in English] You give me a try.
[in Russian] You're vulgar!
Thread 1 is compromised. Help.
[Paldo, in English] This is Thread 3.
[Paldo] I'll take care of the needle.
[Mercado on the device, in English]
The laptop is locked
and requires a code.
Aside from the ambassador,
the only person who knows the code
is the head of IT at the embassy,
Lily Santiago.
UP NEXT
Son of a thread.
[gunshots]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias